It's medically strong.
メジカル強めですね
Is it strong?
強いですか?
So cute.
かわいいな
The clothes are nice too.
服装もいいですね
What kind of edge do you like?
どういうエッジが好きですか?
What kind of edge?
どういうエッジ?
I feel like I'm being blamed.
責められる感じ
Do you want to be blamed?
責められたい?
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
a little bit,
ちょっと、
Does it smell?
匂 う感じですか?
I have a fetish for smells.
匂うフェチなんですよ
is that so?
そうですか?
What?
な になに?
what happened?
どうしたの?
receive.
受ける
I need to check it out a bit.
ちょっと確認しないと
Can I check?
確認していい?
a little bit.
ちょっと
For now.
とりあえずね
Like a greeting.
挨拶みたいな
greeting?
挨拶?
Bag noodles.
袋面
Is the bag surface interesting?
袋面が面白い?
I'm a little bored.
ちょっとつぼっちゃう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It doesn't smell.
匂いしないね
Does the bag side collapse?
袋面がつぼる?
I don't see it.
見ないもんね
Can you blame me?
責められるんですか?
Do you think you're blaming me?
責めてそうだっけ?
yes.
そう
It smells good.
いい匂いする
intense.
激しい
difficult.
難しい
When was the last time you had an edge?
最近いつエッジしたの?
I'll go alone.
一人行っちゃう
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
Awesome.
すげえ
It's so clear.
すけすけですよ
You're tempting me today.
今日誘惑してるね
Did I tempt you?
誘惑しちゃって?
I'm seducing you.
誘惑してる
It's so clear.
すけすけしちゃうんだって
Pikmin?
ピクミン?
Does it smell good?
いい匂いしてる?
It smelled nice though.
いい匂いしてもらいましたけど
Your legs are super beautiful.
超足綺麗じゃん
Wow, beautiful feet.
すげえ足綺麗
It's smooth.
すべすべじゃん
difficult.
難しい
That's amazing.
すごいな
black.
黒い
difficult.
難しい
It's black underwear.
黒い下身なんだ
I like black.
黒好きなんだ
黒好き
It's a foot.
足なの
Because it's white, there's a long wait.
白いから、 待機がすごいらしい
I'm making it difficult.
難しい方にしてる
Nice ass.
いいお尻
I have really nice feet.
めっちゃいい足にしてる
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すごい
Awesome.
すげえ
It's so cool.
すけすけっすよ
cute.
可愛い
It's super cute.
超可愛いね
My abdominal muscles are cracked.
腹筋割れてるね
beautiful.
きれい
As expected.
さすがだね
He's a professional.
プロだね
Do you have abs?
腹筋してる?
I haven't.
してない
That's amazing.
すごいな
Your butt is so curvy.
プリプリだね、お尻
Open your legs.
足開いて
Amazing, beautiful.
すげえ、きれい
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃきれいだね
beautiful.
きれい
Small?
ちっちゃい?
It's small.
ちっちゃいよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
The way you cry is great.
泣い方偉いね
workman
エ
Le Sai.
ル サイ
It didn't fly very well.
すごい飛ばなかった
I slept too much.
寝ろすぎて
Just by looking.
見てるだけで
You didn't touch it just now.
触ってなかったよね、今
I slept too much.
寝ろすぎて
I slept here too much.
ここにも寝ろすぎて
Hey.
ねえ
Did it take?
かかった?
Is it not working?
かかってない?
the sound of the spirit.
精神の音
It feels so good.
すっげえ気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
hey
ね
picture.
え
I'm angry.
怒 です
I'm not satisfied at all.
全 然満足されてない
Because it was impossible.
だって、 無理だったんだもん
That's amazing, I guess.
すごいね、やっぱ
Waist posture.
腰遣いが
腰遣い
Open your legs.
足開いて
Open your hands.
手を開いて
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Because I've gotten this far.
ここまで入っちゃったから